The Yun Kingdom's army has retreated,
لقد انسحب جيش يون
and Zhao Kuo's remaining accomplices
وبقية أتباع تشاو كوو
have all been eliminated by us.
تم القضاء عليهم جميعاً من قبلنا.
Yue'an,
يوه آن
you've worked hard.
لقد تعبت كثيراً.
Kneel down.
اركع.
Within two days,
في غضون يومين
my report will be delivered to the Emperor,
ستصل عريضتي إلى يد الإمبراطور
and then,
وحينها
whether it's dismemberment or being minced into paste,
سواء كان التقطيع أو الفرم والتخليل
you can choose for yourself.
الخيار لك.
You think you've defeated me?
أتظن أنك انتصرت علي؟
Zhao Kuo,
تشاو كوو
give me the antidote for the poison now.
سلمني الآن ترياق السم.
My report is
عريضتي
nothing.
لا شيء.
Are you insane? He committed treason!
هل جننت؟ إنه متمرد!
Once you join the Dark Guards,
بمجرد انضمامك للحرس السري
you'll never escape for the rest of your life.
لن تتمكن من الهروب طوال حياتك.
I've given you a chance to live,
لقد منحتك فرصة للبقاء على قيد الحياة
don't be ungrateful.
فلا تكن وقحاً.
Even if I die,
حتى لو مت
I won't let you succeed.
لن أدعك تنجح بما تريد.
Zhao Kuo!
تشاو كوو!
Yang Tao!
يانغ تاو!
Don't be afraid,
لا تخف
whether I have to go to the Southern Province
سواء ذهبت إلى نان تشو
or to the Eastern Edge,
أو إلى دونغ جي
I will find the antidote for you,
سأجد لك الترياق بالتأكيد
I will save you.
سأنقذك مهما كلف الأمر.
Yang Tao!
يانغ تاو!
That mind-controlling poison
سم فقدان القلب هذا
already makes people delirious,
يسبب الدوار أصلاً
and she forced herself to stay awake,
أجبرت نفسها على الاستيقاظ
which triggered the old poison.
مما أثار السم القديم
Now both poisons are active together,
الآن السمان يعملان معاً
and the toxins have reached her brain.
والسم وصل إلى الدماغ
If we delay any longer,
إذا استمر الوضع هكذا
she won't last six months.
فلن تعيش أكثر من نصف عام
Doctor,
أيها الطبيب
may I have a word with you in private?
أريد التحدث معك على انفراد
Very well.
حسناً.
Is there a cure?
هل هناك علاج؟
It is said that
يُقال
there's a snow lotus in the Northern Territory
أن هناك زهرة ثلجية في الشمال
that can cure this poison.
يمكنها علاج هذا السم.
But that snow lotus is extremely rare,
لكن تلك الزهرة الثلجية نادرة جداً
and often grows in treacherous terrain.
وغالباً ما تنمو في أماكن خطرة وصعبة المنال.
As long as there's a cure,
يكفي أن هناك علاج.
that's all that matters.
هذا جيد أن هناك علاج.
No matter how dangerous or difficult,
مهما كانت المخاطر والصعوبات
I will bring back the snow lotus for her.
سأحضر لها تلك الزهرة الثلجية.
Well,
هذا
this won't be as easy as
ليس سهلاً مثل
treating your headache before.
علاج صداعك في الماضي.
I'll take my leave now.
أستأذن الآن.
Young master,
سيدي
are you mentally ill too?
هل أنت مريض عقلياً أيضاً؟
Why have I never heard you mention this before?
لماذا لم أسمع عن هذا من قبل؟
It happened many years ago.
هذا حدث منذ سنوات عديدة
I'll tell you about it slowly.
سأخبرك القصة ببطء
Are you better now?
هل تحسنت الآن؟
Yes.
نعم، تحسنت
No.
لا
I want to hear it now.
أريد أن أسمع الآن
So?
ما رأيك؟
Does this look familiar to you?
هل لديك ذكريات عن هذا؟
This place here
هنا
is Hele Tower.
هو مطعم هيلي لو
We used to
كنا
come here often to wine and dine.
نأتي إلى هنا دائماً للاستمتاع بالطعام والشراب
Wining and dining
الأكل والشرب
is exactly what I like.
يناسبني تماماً
No wonder we're together.
لا عجب أننا معاً
For you two,
سيداي
I've prepared the Yi room.
لقد جهزت لكما الغرفة رقم اثنين
There won't be any mistakes this time.
هذه المرة لن يكون هناك أي خطأ
Thank you for your help.
شكراً لك
Why is it called Room B?
لماذا يسمى بالغرفة رقم باء؟
And
وأيضاً
why does he look
لماذا يبدو
so afraid of me?
وكأنه خائف مني؟
Excuse me.
اسمحوا لي بالمرور
That's not important.
هذا ليس مهماً
Room B
الغرفة رقم باء
is where we first met.
هي المكان الذي التقينا فيه
Met?
التقينا؟
It's okay.
لا بأس
Let's take it slow.
دعنا نأخذ الأمر ببطء.
It's my fault.
إنه خطأي.
That day,
في ذلك اليوم
I forgot to book this private room.
نسيت حجز هذه الغرفة الخاصة.
This is it,
هذا هو المكان
do you remember?
هل تتذكر؟
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت
to part on good terms,
من أجل أن نفترق بشكل ودي
we pretended to be the Inseparable Heroes,
تظاهرنا بأننا زوج من الأبطال المتحدين
which led to everything else we talked about.
وبعد ذلك حدثت تلك الأشياء التي تحدثنا عنها.
Was Xing Dezheng deliberately setting us up?
هل كان شينغ دي تشينغ يتعمد الإيقاع بنا؟
This room
هذا المنزل
was booked by Butcher Zhang.
حجزه الجزار تشانغ.
How should I put it,
كيف أقول هذا
it was fate, I suppose.
إنه قدر محتوم.
So we're innocent now, right?
إذن نحن أبرياء الآن، أليس كذلك؟
Of course we are innocent.
بالتأكيد نحن أبرياء.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا
we'll live freely and follow our hearts.
سنعيش حياة حرة كما نشاء.
Wherever you want to go,
في المستقبل، أينما تريد الذهاب للاستمتاع
we'll go there,
يمكنك الذهاب إلى هناك
no one will ever restrict our freedom again.
لن يستطيع أحد تقييد حريتنا بعد الآن.
How did you know I've always wanted to travel the world?
كيف عرفت أنني طالما رغبت في استكشاف الجبال والأنهار
Even the doctor today suggested I should get out more.
حتى الطبيب اليوم نصحني بالتجول في كل مكان.
That's why
لذلك
I submitted my resignation to the court today.
قدمت اليوم عريضة إلى البلاط الملكي.
From now on, court affairs
شؤون البلاط الملكي من الآن فصاعدًا
have nothing to do with me.
لم تعد تخصني.
Then
إذن
what about the northern border?
ماذا عن الحدود الشمالية؟
Yue'an is there,
يوي آن موجودة
with her in charge,
بوجودها هناك
I can rest easy.
أنا مطمئن.
Taotao.
تاو تاو.
In my life,
في حياتي هذه
there are many things I want to do.
هناك الكثير من الأشياء التي أرغب في القيام بها.
Wherever you go from now on,
في المستقبل، أينما تذهب
I'll go with you,
سأذهب معك
we'll never be apart again in this lifetime.
لن نفترق أبدًا في هذه الحياة.
Okay.
حسنًا.
We'll never be apart.
لن نفترق أبدًا.
Sorry to interrupt you lovebirds
آسف على مقاطعة حديثكما الخاص أيها العاشقان
having your private conversation.
أعتذر حقًا عن ذلك
But there's an imperial decree
لكن هناك أمر ملكي
that I must announce.
يجب أن أعلنه
Zhao Jian.
الأخ تشاو جيان
Chunran-
الأخت تشون ران-
I haven't seen you for so long.
لم أرك منذ وقت طويل
I've missed you terribly.
اشتقت إليك كثيرًا
This is not
هذا ليس
what it seems.
كذلك
Speak properly.
تكلم بشكل لائق
We're not kids anymore.
لم نعد أطفالاً
Why are you here?
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
I'm just making an announcement.
أليس هذا إعلاناً رسمياً
They said you were here,
قالوا إنك هنا
so I came.
لذلك جئت
Princess Chunran,
الأميرة تشون ران
stop making trouble.
كفي عن هذه المشاغبة
When I first met her, she was only
عندما تعرفت عليها كانت
this tall.
بهذا الطول فقط
Seems like you have quite a few sisters.
يبدو أن لديك أخوات كثيرات.
What else don't I know about?
ما الذي لا أعرفه بعد؟
By order of His Majesty,
أنقل أوامر الإمبراطور الشفهية،
the Crown Prince of Luling,
وريث أمير لولينغ،
Zhao Jian and his wife have rendered meritorious service to the nation,
الزوجان تشاو جيان قدما خدمات جليلة للبلاد،
and their new titles and rewards
وأمر ترقيتهما ومكافأتهما،
will be arranged by the Ministry of Personnel.
ستتولاه وزارة شؤون الموظفين.
As for what follows,
أما الكلام التالي،
I must speak more quietly.
فسأخفض صوتي قليلاً.
The Kingdom of Yun still harbors evil intentions
مملكة يون لم تتخل عن نواياها الشريرة،
and continues to send people to harass our borders.
وما زالت ترسل رجالها لاختراق حدودنا،
A storm is brewing.
العاصفة تقترب،
You two are ordered
لذا عليكما أنتما الزوجان،
to immediately assume the identities
أن تحلا فوراً محل،
of the Inseparable Heroes
الفارسين المتلازمين،
under the pretense that they have faked their deaths and escaped,
بحجة هروبهما بعد تظاهرهما بالموت،
and infiltrate the Kingdom of Yun.
والتسلل إلى مملكة يون،
Ensure that all affairs of Yun,
لتجعلا كل أمور مملكة يون صغيرها وكبيرها،
great and small, are made known to me.
معروفة لدينا تماماً.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعداً،
you
أنتما،
are truly
ستصبحان حقاً،
the Inseparable Heroes.
الفارسين المتلازمين.
From now on.
من الآن،
rests in your hands.
يعتمد عليكما.
Sir Wang.
سيد وانغ
The thing is,
الأمر هكذا.
the person you're looking for
الشخص الذي تبحثون عنه
is named Zhao Jian.
اسمه تشاو جيان.
And I
أما أنا
am
فـ
Chen Yiqu.
تشين يي تشو.
Are you defying the imperial order?
هل تريد أن تعصي أمر الإمبراطور؟
That sounds interesting.
أعتقد أن هذا يبدو ممتعاً
Why don't we go?
هيا بنا نذهب.
Do you know what the Twin Heroes are?
هل تعرف ما هو ثنائي الفرسان جيان دي؟
The Twin Heroes are
ثنائي الفرسان جيان دي هما
the birds that fly wing to wing and the fish that swim eye to eye,
طائر بي يي وسمكة بي مو
one in the sky and one in the sea,
واحد في السماء والآخر في الأرض
isn't that fascinating?
هذا مثير للاهتمام، أليس كذلك؟
But Yun Kingdom is so far away and dangerous.
لكن مملكة يون بعيدة وخطيرة جداً.
Stop talking,
لا تتحدث بعد
we've received the imperial decree.
لقد تلقينا الأمر الملكي.
All right.
حسناً.
I'm going too.
سأذهب أيضاً.